[
  {
    "question": "Which file format can be added to a PowerPoint show?",
    "correct_answer": ".pptx",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      ".txt",
      ".docx",
      ".pdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a motion path in PowerPoint?",
    "correct_answer": "What is a motion path in PowerPoint",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      " A visual representation of the slide's background, according to Scribd.",
      "A feature that allows you to add notes to your slides, according to Scribd.",
      "A way to organize your slides into sections, according to Scribd."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a slide master?",
    "correct_answer": "A template that controls the look and feel of all slides in a presentation.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The first slide in a presentation.",
      "A type of animation that can be applied to text.",
      "A feature that allows you to add comments to your slides."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a slide layout element?",
    "correct_answer": "Animations",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Titles",
      "Lists",
      "Charts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of slide transitions?",
    "correct_answer": "To control the way one slide moves to the next.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      " To add animations to objects on a slide..",
      "To add sounds to your presentation.",
      "To create custom animations."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you add images to a PowerPoint slide?",
    "correct_answer": "All of the above.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "By using the Insert > Picture option.",
      "By dragging and dropping the image file onto the slide.",
      " By copying and pasting the image into the slide."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the \"5/5/5\" rule refer to in PowerPoint design?",
    "correct_answer": "No more than 5 words per line, 5 lines per slide, and 5 text-heavy slides in a row.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "No more than 5 minutes of presentation time, 5 words per line, and 5 lines per slide.",
      "No more than 5 slides per presentation, 5 words per line, and 5 minutes of presentation time.",
      "No more than 5 seconds of animation per slide, 5 words per line, and 5 minutes of presentation time. "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "From which menu can you access Text Box, Picture, Chart etc.?",
    "correct_answer": "Insert",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "View",
      "Edit",
      "File"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following font effects is NOT available in the PowerPoint Font dialog box?",
    "correct_answer": "Strikethrough ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Shadow",
      "Underline",
      "Emboss"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you use if you want to add text to a slide?",
    "correct_answer": "Text Box",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Comment Box",
      "Text layer",
      "Note Book"
    ]
  }
]